[musical swirl]
[gentle music]
[peaceful vocalizing]
[birds chirping]
[gentle music]
[David sighing]
[David chuckling]
[distant bleating]
[David gasping] [exciting music]
Oh boy.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy,
oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Ha ha!
It's time!
Stand aside, stand
aside, Gibor! Ha ha!
Thank you, Abirra.
Thank you, Yala.
[exciting music]
Oh! Hey, hey, hey, Shira.
Don't worry, I got you.
You're a bit early,
aren't you girl?
Stand back, everyone.
The flock's about to
get a little bigger.
[foreboding music]
It's okay girl, you're good.
Just breathe.
We'll get this little one out,
then I promise...
[bushes rustling]
I'll bring you home.
[stoic music]
[David whistling]
[sheep bleating]
[foreboding music]
Stay together.
If we stay close, stay tight,
it won't be able to
single anyone out.
[tense music]
I can't do this alone.
[suspenseful music]
[sheep bleating]
No, wait!
[suspenseful music]
[sheep bleating]
[David grunting]
[triumphant music]
[tense music]
[lion growls]
Just stay quiet girl.
He hasn't seen you.
[tense music]
That's it.
Eyes on me.
On...
Me.
[Shira bleating]
No, no, no, no!
[lion growling]
No!
[suspenseful music]
[David yelling]
No! [Grunts]
God spoke to me.
Eh, it comes with
being a prophet.
Oh!
He told me very clearly
[Shimea gasping]
that I was to come
to this very house
and anoint a son of Jesse
to be the next king.
[Nethanel and Ozem gasping]
But [sighs]
it is none of these.
[Samuel chuckles]
That one had potential
though. [Chuckles]
[Zeruiah giggling]
Unless, perhaps you
have another son?
[curious music]
[David moaning]
[David gasping]
Oh, no.
Shira.
Shira!
[sorrowful music]
No!
[David sobbing]
Shira. [Sobs]
I'm so sorry. [Sobs]
[David sobbing] [lamb bleating]
Huh? What? [Gentle
wondrous music]
Shira?
Shira, you're alive?!
Oh.
[lion growling] [David gasping]
[lamb bleating]
[gentle wondrous music]
[swelling wondrous music]
Oh, ho, ho!
That'll teach you to
mess with my sheep.
Whoo!
I'm so glad you're okay.
And who is this little one?
[David and lamb giggling]
Oh. Oh, she's my lamb, is she?
Tali. [Tali giggling]
Well, Tali.
Let's go and introduce you to
the others and get you home.
[lion helplessly growls]
[Tali cooing]
Wait here, girl.
[gentle music] [birds singing]
[growling]
[David grunting] [hopeful music]
[triumphant music]
[David grunting]
[David laughing]
Whew.
[gentle music]
Whooo! Ha ha.
Now, where are the others?
[bleating]
Hey! Hey, it's okay,
he's gone, you're safe.
You can come out now.
[sheep bleating]
Don't you want to come out?
Meet the new baby?
[Tali bleating]
[sighs] I know that was scary,
but doesn't it make
you feel more alive?
And do you know what?
I don't see a bunch
of scared sheep.
Do you know what I see?
Mighty horses! Ready
to take on the world!
[sheep bleating]
I'm scared too sometimes,
but somewhere deep
down, I know...
♪ There's a light
in the distance ♪
♪ And if you listen ♪
♪ You'll hear it
calling your name ♪
♪ It takes courage to follow ♪
♪ But trust me and lets go ♪
♪ And you'll see the
world start to change ♪
♪ So don't waste a
moment on staying ♪
♪ Too focused on
problems that might ♪
♪ Be ahead ♪
♪ And when it gets dark ♪
♪ Don't ever let
your heart forget ♪
♪ To run, run,
toward adventure ♪
♪ To whatever comes your way ♪
♪ Come on and taste the
kind of freedom ♪
♪ Only the wilderness contains ♪
♪ Don't care if
people call us crazy ♪
♪ What's the fun
in playing safe ♪
♪ I wanna run, run, run ♪
♪ Feel the wind blowing ♪
♪ The sun in your eyes ♪
♪ And breathe in
those mercies so new ♪
[David laughing]
♪ Come on, can't you see it ♪
♪ Those wide open skies ♪
♪ They call and my
feet have to move ♪
♪ I wasn't called to be
caged by four walls ♪
♪ I'm exactly where
I want to be ♪
♪ If my future was up to me ♪
♪ I'd only want to be free, oh ♪
♪ I wanna run, run
with the horses ♪
♪ Through the water
and the flame ♪
♪ What's to fear when
Heaven's with me ♪
♪ When the unknown
calls my name ♪
♪ I wanna climb the
highest mountain ♪
♪ Face whatever comes my way ♪
♪ I wanna run, run, run ♪
Hoo! Okay.
Alright guys.
So on the count of three...
We're all going to run.
[hooves beating]
I... I didn't say three yet!
Guys!
Okay, slow down! Here I come!
[bright upbeat
music] [David laughs]
♪ I want to run, run
toward adventure ♪
- ♪ To whatever comes my way ♪
- David's coming!
♪ I want to taste
the kind of freedom ♪
- ♪ Only the wilderness contains
♪ - Ooh, everyday!
♪ Don't care if
people call me crazy ♪
[Bethlehem Man] You're crazy!
♪ What's the fun
in playing safe ♪
[Bethlehem Townsfolk 2]
Get out of the way!
♪ I wanna run, run, run ♪
[ground rumbling]
[household murmuring]
[Nitzevet gasping]
Oh no.
[Eliab sighing]
[Nethanel] Oh, the food!
Please not the food!
[household murmuring]
[household exclaiming]
Whoa! Coming in!
Oof!
[Zeruiah] David! [Giggles]
[happy music] [Zeruiah giggling]
[David laughing] [goat bleating]
A goat? When did we get a goat?
Huh?
Hmm.
Er. Sh-Shalom.
It-It wasn't me.
[goat bleating]
And if it was, I can explain.
Maybe.
Uh, what's happening?
Remember when I told you
God had big plans for you?
[Nitzevet laughing]
Well, they may have been
bigger than even I thought.
[Samuel] David,
son of Jesse.
Are you ready for
a great adventure?
Uh, yes!
As King of Israel.
What? No.
No?
No, no, no, no.
Don't mess this
up for me, David.
If you're king, then I
get to be a princess.
[David scoffing]
I can't be king.
We already have a king.
That's right.
Which makes this treason.
[Abinadab laughing]
Oh, now it's treason?
And, uh, what was it when
he was considering you?
Ugh, I am a soldier
in Saul's army!
I have been nothing but
faithful to my father,
King Saul, and God!
That is wonderful.
Continue to do so.
You can't take the youngest
and elevate him
above the rest of us!
Do you want me to take his place
and shepherd the flock again?
No, Ozem will take
over shepherding.
Wait, what?
No. Nethanel can do it.
I'm not doing it.
The twins can do it.
- Don't bring us into this.
- Yeah.
- Boys.
- Whatever.
Don't look at me.
[Brothers grumbling]
- Way to go.
- Way to go, David.
Boys. [Staff slamming]
Sorry.
I like it. Do it again.
I do not come here lightly.
The very hearts of the
people are at stake.
There is the darkness
over the land.
Philistines?
The Philistines are
a threat, to be sure.
[apprehensive music]
They lord over us
with power and pride.
[bleating]
But there is a graver
danger we face.
Amalekites?
The Amalekites are
nothing but scavengers.
And they are always watching,
always waiting in the shadows.
Just as they preyed on
the weak and vulnerable
when we escaped Pharaoh,
they wait for us to be divided,
for the sheep to scatter
and they will strike once more.
[ominous music]
But our true battle is not
against flesh and blood,
but in our hearts.
Did our enemies make
us turn away from God?
No. We demanded a king.
So, God gave us King Saul
whose love of the crown
has consumed him.
And now, we see the cost
of putting our faith in man.
Philistines, Amalekites,
Saul.
We are hard pressed
on every side.
But at last,
God has chosen another.
Someone with a heart after His.
But I don't want to be king.
That is surprisingly
good criteria for a king.
I'm just a shepherd.
The people are lost, David.
Astray in a storm.
A shepherd [chuckles]
is precisely who they need.
But God is my shepherd.
He's who we need.
Every excuse you give
is another reason
it must be you.
But... Yes?
[David sighing]
Stand before me, son of Jesse.
[calm music]
♪ Ba-ruch haba ♪
♪ B'shem Adonai ♪
♪ Bay-rach-nu-chem ♪
♪ Mi-bayt Adonai ♪
♪ Hodu Ladonai ♪
♪ Ki-tov ♪
♪ Ki L'olam ♪
♪ Chasdo ♪
[hopeful music]
So, what happens now?
Do Saul and David
fight to the death?
No. No.
This is a gift that
must remain secret.
[knuckles rapping]
[household gasping]
[Scout] We have heard
about David's gift.
He must come before
King Saul at once.
They couldn't have known.
What have you
brought on our house?
They cannot know I'm here.
If Saul finds out about this,
none of you will be safe.
[Jesse] Zeruiah, no!
[Zeruiah] Who goes there?
It is I, Princess Zeruiah.
Hmph, is David here?
Get out of here.
We'll distract him.
Sh-Shalom.
King Saul is greatly disturbed.
David must come with me at once.
I- I-Look, David is.
Here.
I'm right here.
Oh, dear boy.
He is going to eat you alive.
[solemn music]
[Townsperson] Welcome to Gibeah.
[Vendor] Hey, you.
[Fruit Vendor] Strawberries!
Get your fresh picked
strawberries here!
Get your fresh fruit here!
[wondrous music]
[townsfolk shouting]
[wondrous music continues]
[Builder] Here we go.
- On the count of three.
- Come on.
Get some more tension
into that line, boys!
All right.
[Abner] Finally, you're here!
[wondrous music]
[Townsperson 1] Where
do you want this one?
[Townsperson 2] Just
like that. Good, good.
[townsfolk murmuring]
Woo-hoo-hoo!
This is the one from
Bethlehem, Your Grace.
Where is your instrument?
Er, instrument?
You can't exactly
play for my husband
without an instrument.
Play?
And you can't go
before him like this.
What's in your hair?
Oil?
Uh. Whoa.
[water splashes]
Whoo!
[David breathes heavy]
Sorry.
Oh, not at all.
In fact, here, why don't
you stand in front of me?
Oh, okay.
Wait a second.
Where do you think
you are going?
Prince Jonathan,
we really must see your
father quite urgently.
Now's really not the best time.
The affairs of state
cannot be put on hold
while you pacify your father's.
[Saul] Do you think
this is helping me?!
[musician whimpering]
We'll put the affairs
of state on hold now.
Clearly it's not the best time.
What's going on?
Saul called for every
musician in the kingdom.
Music used to soothe him.
[Saul] Get out, and
don't come back!
[musician whimpering]
Yes, Your Highness.
Ah, why don't you take my place?
Oh, please. In front of me.
No, I insist. Take my place.
- Don't let me get in your way.
- Up to the front.
Ah.
Hey, kid.
What are you doing here?
[Saul] Next!
[crashing]
I guess it's your turn.
[quiet music]
[doors slamming]
[gasps] Shhhh...
[Saul mumbling]
They think a child can help me?
[somber music]
Are you going to sing, or what?
Well I... I don't have my...
If I could just...
[Saul grunting]
Get out!
[metal clacking]
[somber music] [David grunts]
[sighs] Next.
No, wait!
Can I borrow this? Thank you.
[scoffs] You're
going back in there?
I know right? [Laughs]
[light instrumental music]
Huh? Why are you back here?
Because now I've got this.
Just leave me in peace.
I'm gonna try.
[light music begins]
♪ When I feel lost ♪
♪ And so afraid ♪
♪ And shadows have
hid the sun away ♪
♪ When my heart is heavy ♪
♪ And it's hard to pray ♪
♪ I remember what my
mother used to say ♪
♪ Shalom ♪
♪ Peace be with you ♪
♪ Wherever you go ♪
♪ Shalom ♪
♪ Let this melody ♪
♪ Begin to bring you home ♪
[light instrumental music]
♪ In desperation ♪
♪ When you're losing sight ♪
♪ You've cried out
with everything inside ♪
♪ There is still a shepherd ♪
♪ Even when you hide ♪
♪ Who will pick you up and
hold you till you find ♪
♪ Shalom Shalom ♪
♪ Peace be with you
wherever you go ♪
♪ Shalom Shalom ♪
♪ Let this melody begin
to bring you home ♪
♪ Let this melody bring you ♪
♪ Shalom ♪
[light instrumental music]
He-he-he didn't like it.
[musicians muttering
and screaming]
[Saul sighing]
[footsteps thumping]
What's your name?
David.
Well David, I can't remember
the last time I
felt like that...
[inhales sharply] Free.
You know, I never
asked for this.
I didn't want to be king.
Me neither.
I mean, I can imagine.
[scoffs] Can you, David?
One minute you're tending
your father's donkeys,
the next Samuel anoints
you to be king of Israel.
[light inspirational music]
[people chattering]
And then, after all these years,
after all I've done for Israel
he tries to-to take it from me,
says he's going to
give it to another.
If I get my hands
on that prophet.
If I find out who it is Samuel
has chosen to replace me...
[light instrumental
music] [Saul sighing]
But then you came along.
[dramatic music]
Father, the Philistines.
The Philistines amass for war.
[Saul laughing]
Today is a bad day for
them to pick a fight.
Ready my horse.
David, you have done your
king a great service.
Return to your fields.
And while you're there, write
a victory song for my return.
[bright dramatic
music] [men muttering]
[wooden weapons clumping]
This is not what
I signed up for.
So this is not
going to end well.
Come on men.
Spirits up, you are mighty
soldiers in the Israelite army.
If by mighty you mean scared
and by soldiers you mean
farmers, then sure, that's us.
You underestimate
who's on our side.
Do you see this, Jonathan?
We haven't even faced
the Philistines yet.
I did this to myself, with this.
It's not even a real weapon.
- Ow.
- I am so sorry. Are you okay?
- Yup, we're dead.
- Have a little faith men.
Oh I do have a little
faith, very little.
[bright inspirational music]
[Army cheering] [dramatic music]
[drums banging]
[army chanting] [dramatic music]
Saul, Saul, Saul.
I thought we had an agreement.
I allow you and
your little tribes
to live in this land and you
I know our agreement Achish.
We pay your taxes,
we get our tools sharpened
by your blacksmiths.
Well I must say, a
lot of your tools
are looking very pointy.
That was not part
of our arrangement.
Well, perhaps it's time
to come to new terms.
Ooh, those are
fighting words Saul.
Your army is clearly
no match for mine.
I would rather
not kill all those
potential workers for my fields,
so why don't we
make this simpler?
Your best warrior, against mine?
Father, you're more than
a match for any Philistine.
Besides, God fights for us.
[scoffs] So be it.
Choose your man
to fight, Achish.
Good. [Laughs]
Very good. Very, very,
very good. [Laughs]
Deal. [Laughs]
Bring out Goliath.
[dramatic music] [army chanting]
He's huge.
Oh, that's not him.
That's his armor bearer.
[giant grunting]
[light dramatic music]
[feet thumping]
[horses neighing]
[light dramatic music]
[Goliath grunting]
- He's huge.
- Like a mountain.
He's the biggest
thing I've ever seen,
and I once seen a whale.
[light dramatic music]
I like horses.
Not much else will
fill me up. [Grunts]
[horses neighing]
[Goliath laughing]
[army chanting] [dramatic music]
This day, Goliath defies
the ranks of Israel.
Choose a man to fight me.
If he wins, the Philistines
will be your subjects.
If I beat him,
you will serve us.
[dramatic music]
Summon my advisors.
[Goliath laughing]
Don't worry, take your time.
Goliath is nothing if not
patient.
[dramatic music]
[David sighing]
[carriage rattling]
[light instrumental music]
Shimea get an Ephah of grain.
[Shimea] What's an Ephah?
Ozem, the sheep.
[Ozem groaning]
[Zeruiah giggling] [Ozem crying]
Ima, Ima, look.
Yes, dear. It's beautiful.
Hmm, stress weaving again?
[scoffs] I'm allowed.
Eliab and Abinadab have
been called to war,
I still don't know
what happening with...
[David whistling]
[Nitzevet gasping]
David.
David!
Oh yay. Ow.
[light instrumental music]
[sheep bleating]
Oh, I missed you guys.
Are you king yet?
Do you have a crown?
Can I wear it?
[laughs] No.
David.
It's a relief to see
you in one piece.
Are you all right?
Did he find out
about the anointing?
[gasps] Have you eaten?
Is the family in danger?
[gasps] They touched your hair.
What happened with Saul?
Nothing happened.
What's going on here?
Well, the town has been
asked for supplies for the war.
Where are the supplies?
I got hungry.
From the house to the donkey?
Huh-uh-uh. Where do
you think you're going?
You haven't told me
what happened yet.
Nothing, it's all okay.
I just want to head
back to the fields.
Saul was troubled
and I played for him,
[scoffs] that's all.
[Nitzevet clears throat]
[light instrumental music]
[David sighing]
I just... The whole
time I was in Gibeah,
nothing made sense.
Am I meant to lie?
Am I meant to help
Saul, or hate him,
or obey him, or fight him?
[David coughing]
I just don't know!
Things are simple out there.
Everything makes sense.
But with the anointing,
with the king thing
[sighs] I just don't
understand what God's doing.
[giggles] Nor do I.
And that's why I do this.
Stress-weaving again?
That's not the point.
Look here. Beautiful isn't it?
Um, it's not your best.
[giggles] Every
thread has a purpose.
They all have a place.
It looks messy, but when
you see the finished picture
on the other side,
they all make sense.
You're just like one
of these threads.
[Zeruiah gasping]
Am even I there?
Yup, here you are
and there's Tali.
Yes Ozem, even you.
Uh, Ima. [Nitzevet laughs]
I love you.
[Ozem] Ima!
[Zeruiah laughing
and exclaiming]
Hey let me see.
Nope, it's not finished yet.
Play me something.
But... [stammers]
Go on, something new.
♪ I don't know what to play ♪
♪ That's okay ♪
♪ This is just a random phrase ♪
♪ But it sounds good anyway ♪
♪ No song arrives
fully written ♪
♪ No pot begins fully formed ♪
Are you calling me a pot?
Kind of...
[man grunting]
♪ But you're so much more ♪
♪ The sheep they do not
know where they are going ♪
♪ but they're following the
shepherd where he leads ♪
♪ The flower does not
know how it is growing ♪
♪ But the rain still falls
and gives it what it needs ♪
♪ There's a reason for the
colors in your story ♪
♪ There's a picture though
you cannot see it yet ♪
♪ Every thread has a purpose
and soon you'll see ♪
♪ Your part in this tapestry ♪
[sheep bleating]
Hey, hey!
♪ And when you feel like
nothing is connecting ♪
♪ And you're searching for
an answer you can't find ♪
♪ Just remember that each
strand is intersecting ♪
♪ To reveal what the creator
has designed ♪
♪ Any masterpiece is gonna
take some time ♪
♪ There's a reason for the
colors in your story ♪
♪ If there's a reason ♪
♪ I can't find it ♪
♪ There's a picture though ♪
♪ You cannot see it yet ♪
♪ Sure I believe ♪
♪ That every thread
has a purpose ♪
♪ But I don't see ♪
♪ Soon you'll see ♪
♪ Your part in this tapestry ♪
♪ So lift your eyes
above the hills ♪
♪ Higher up and higher still ♪
♪ If you could see
from heaven's view ♪
♪ All the plans
drawn out for you ♪
♪ Like the way we
work the loom ♪
♪ He knits you from
inside the womb ♪
♪ Every string is
used in His design ♪
♪ I lift my eyes
above the hills ♪
♪ Though it's not
clear I know I will ♪
♪ Catch the view
that heaven sees ♪
♪ And leap into
His plans for me ♪
♪ I'll find out where ♪
♪ This story goes
♪ ♪ Now you see ♪
♪ I'm not there yet ♪
♪ But now I know
♪ ♪ Just believe ♪
♪ The One who brought ♪
♪ this world to
life ♪ ♪ Adonai ♪
♪ Has seen it all ♪
♪ before it's time
♪ ♪ Perfect time ♪
♪ So ready or not,
come what may ♪
♪ I'll face whatever
may come my way ♪
♪ 'Cause everything is
used in His design ♪
♪ There's a reason for
the colors in my story ♪
♪ El Shaddai will be your
guide when you can't see ♪
♪ Every thread has a
purpose and I believe ♪
♪ I'm part of this ♪ ♪
You're part in this ♪
♪ Tapestry ♪
♪ We're part of this ♪
What are you two singing for?
There is carrying to be done.
Someone needs to take
our supplies to the army.
They wouldn't arrive with
Nethanel, perhaps Ozem?
[Ozem groaning] [David laughing]
I know who can take it, right?
[Tali bleating] [light
instrumental music]
[David sighing] [light
[Nitzevet giggling]
[light instrumental music]
Here, look after Tali
for me won't you?
[David giggles] [light
instrumental music]
Right.
Wait, where's David going?
[Ozem groaning]
[sheep bleating]
[light instrumental music]
[transitions to dramatic music]
[Townsman] Fresh
supplies over here.
[crowd chattering]
Hey kid, over here!
[Goliath] I laugh
while you cower. [Laughs]
[Townsman] Where are you going?
[dramatic music]
[crowd chattering]
Excuse me. [Grunts]
[Eliab] David!
What are you doing here?
I brought cheese and bread.
Ooh, and figs.
[Goliath] I defeat you
without lifting a finger.
[Goliath laughing]
Who's doing all the shouting?
You are putting the
whole family in danger
by being here to
what? Watch a battle?
Oh calm down Eliab,
who wouldn't want to see
the glorious Israelite
army in action?
[Goliath laughing]
[Goliath] You are
an army of cowards.
- He's not wrong.
- Fair point, fair point.
[Goliath] Not even your
God can save you
from the might of
the Philistines.
Oh yeah? Come over here
and we'll see about that.
Sh-sh-shhh, Goliath
might hear you.
Who's Goliath?
Imagine the biggest
warrior you have ever seen.
Okay?
Now imagine somebody ate him.
It doesn't matter how big he is.
With God on our side,
even I could fight him.
- You?
- Yes.
[crowd laughing]
He thinks he can beat
Goliath! [Laughs]
With God fighting for us it
could be you, or you, or you.
Me? [Yells]
[crowd laughing]
[Soldier] Well, looks
like it's going to be you.
[crowd laughing]
[David grunting]
[Goliath] I cannot wait to
see who you send to face me.
What about our new
treaty proposal?
Sire, with all due respect,
King Achish knows he
has the upper hand.
He will not be interested
in a new treaty.
Yes, but was it
presented to him?
What did he say?
He said, "I have the upper hand,
and I am not interested
in a new treaty."
Father, we're out of options.
I will go and fight him.
I will not send my son
on a suicide mission.
This Philistine is no
match for the God of Israel.
I said no!
[crowd laughing]
[light instrumental music]
You again?
A song can do little here, boy.
I haven't come to sing.
Then why are you here?
I- I will fight Goliath.
[everyone laughing]
I'm serious. I
will fight Goliath.
Ah David. Once again you
have lightened my spirits.
Your presence here
is most welcome.
You're so small.
What difference does
size make to a giant?
[Goliath] I will rip
him limb from limb.
You're not afraid to
go out there alone?
I won't be alone.
Oh this is ridiculous.
Just look at him.
Yeah, look at me.
I've fought lions and bears, Me!
God protected me when they
came for my father's sheep,
and He will do the
same against Goliath.
And I saw him tame one other
beast when no others could.
Is that what I've
become, a beast?
I know who you really are.
The one God chose
to lead His people.
I know you still
recognize His voice.
What is it telling you?
[Goliath laughing]
Sire, you cannot
be considering...
Suit him up.
[light instrumental music]
But sire...
Or you could go, if you want?
[trembles] Get him ready.
[clapping hands]
[David grunting]
[Goliath] I defeat you without.
[David] Is that really
necessary? Okay.
Today we will see if
God is still with us...
Or not.
[grunts] I can't go out in this.
You're right, there
are still too many gaps.
Here, here, and here.
[light instrumental music]
[metal clanking]
Much better.
Yes, but can he move?
Of course he can.
You can, can't you?
David?
[clanking]
Oh dear.
[Goliath] Who's it
going to be, Saul?
[Saul grunting] [light
instrumental music]
[footsteps thumping]
[water pattering]
[birds chirping]
[David sighing]
[light instrumental music]
Huh.
[David humming]
[footstep thumping]
[water pattering]
[David humming]
♪ I will not be afraid... ♪
[dramatic music builds]
Uh-oh.
[Eliab] David, you fool.
[dramatic music]
[Philistine army chanting]
[light instrumental music]
[soldiers grunting]
Silence.
[birds chirping]
[Goliath grunting]
[light instrumental music]
Uh, where are you going?
[sighs] This is an insult.
Yes, a great insult.
An insult you should crush.
A child? You expect
me to fight a child?
No. No no no no.
No, no way. No, of course not.
[King Achish laughs]
But yes, that's exactly
what I expect you to do.
[Goliath grunting]
Do you think this is a game?
[sighs] I will make you
a snack for the crows.
[Philistine army laughing]
Or maybe they'll
get a giant feast.
[Philistine army exclaiming]
[Goliath grunting]
I suppose it would be a shame
to have come all
this way for nothing.
[laughs] Marvelous.
[Philistine army cheering]
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
[Goliath yelling]
[dramatic music] [feet thumping]
[Goliath grunting]
Oops, missed.
[Philistine army laughing]
Are you sure you want
to continue this, kid?
You don't even
have a real weapon.
Maybe he can't lift one.
[soldier laughing]
You think your weapons
can do anything
against the God
who parted the sea?
The God who came in
a pillar of fire?
Wait, what are you saying?
You come against me
with sword and spear,
but I come against you
in the name of the God
of heaven and earth.
The battle is His and He
will give you into our hands.
[Goliath grunts]
[Goliath laughing]
By Dagon. Here I was
thinking that Saul had sent
a boy to do a man's job.
While actually, he was
setting me up to fight a God.
[Goliath laughing]
[soldiers laughing]
Well that's more like it.
This I can get behind.
Who would like to see
Goliath take on a God!
[Philistine army cheering]
[light instrumental music]
[grunts] I accept
Your challenge.
And I now challenge You to
show Yourself and let us fight.
Come down here, Israelite God,
and I will make you kneel
before the might of Goliath!
[gentle music]
[inspirational music]
Ah!
[Goliath grunts]
[Goliath groans]
[body thuds]
[all gasp]
[King Achish rattled]
Do you really think one stone
is enough to defeat
my entire army?
[dramatic music]
[people screaming]
[uplifting music]
Yaah!
Hm?
[people screaming]
Did you see that, Eliab.
That's our brother!
God is with him, father.
God is with him!
Yaahhh!
[people screaming]
I told you.
[goat bleating]
But now he will need God
more than ever.
Please. Look after him.
[crowd cheering]
[Farmer Soldier] It's the king!
Here comes the king!
[crowd cheering]
[Crowd] David! David! David!
David, you saved us!
I lent him my lyre, you know.
You're our champion!
He is brave, he is true.
No!
- No?
No! It's not about me.
And he's so humble too!
[Crowd] David! David! David!
No!
Don't look at me, look at God.
Just look at him, the
way he looks at God.
No, you don't get it.
What don't we get?
- We don't get it.
- Tell us!
But he does!
[Crowd] Yeah tell us.
Okay, okay, listen, listen!
Everyone quiet!
David's going to speak!
Er... [chuckles]
Would you mind?
[gentle music]
♪ There's a light
I've always followed ♪
♪ When I'm looking for the way ♪
♪ When I'm searching
for the answer ♪
♪ In the moments I'm afraid ♪
♪ There's a whisper in the wind
and a story in the sky ♪
♪ When I'm looking for a lantern
to illuminate the night ♪
♪ If you want the secret of
freedom and feeling alive ♪
♪ You gotta follow the light ♪
♪ Follow the light ♪
♪ Feel the rushing wind as
you're running into the wild ♪
That's right, yeah!
♪ We'll see the sun
rise out of the ash ♪
♪ As we hold nothing back ♪
♪ When the shadows come,
we won't run from the fight ♪
♪ Come on and follow the light ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪ ♪ Oh ♪
♪ Come on and follow the light ♪
♪ If there's one thing that I
know, I'm nothing but a man ♪
♪ With the heart of a lion
and the spirit of a lamb ♪
♪ Every battle that I've won,
every giant that I've faced ♪
♪ I have never been alone,
even on my darkest day ♪
♪ If you want the secret of
freedom and feeling alive ♪
♪ You gotta follow the light ♪
♪ Follow the light ♪
♪ Feel the rushing wind as
you're running into the wild ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We'll see the sun rise ♪
♪ Out of the ash ♪
♪ As we hold nothing back ♪
♪ When the shadows come,
we won't run from the fight ♪
♪ So come on and
follow the light ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[Jonathan grunts]
♪ Come on and follow the light ♪
[David laughs]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Come on and follow the light ♪
Fire! ♪ One step,
one leap of faith, ♪
Look! ♪ Letting go
is all it takes ♪
♪ Running with the One
who hears your voice ♪
♪ And makes the
mountains shake ♪
♪ When you can't see the road,
there's a fire in your soul ♪
♪ Trust and let it guide
you anywhere you go ♪
♪ You gotta follow the light ♪
♪ Follow the light ♪
♪ Feel the rushing wind as
you're running into the wild ♪
[child laughs]
♪ Oh, yeah ♪ ♪ We'll
see the sun rise ♪
♪ Out of the ash ♪
♪ As we hold nothing back ♪
♪ When the shadows come,
we won't run from the fight ♪
[David laughs]
♪ So come on and
follow the light ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Come on and follow ♪
♪ Come on and follow
the light ♪ ♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Come on and follow the light ♪
[crowd cheering]
David!
You have given our people
hope once more!
We have never been so united.
Now is the time
to fully establish
the glory of our kingdom!
[crowd cheers]
We will strike each
Philistine outpost.
Starting with Ziklag.
We will crush them underfoot,
the way they once crushed us!
[crowd cheering]
And who better to lead us
into battle than David!
My king, would you
like us to enquire of God
if this is His will?
[Saul sighs]
I am God's anointed king.
My bidding is His will.
[dramatic music]
[Saul screams]
[soldiers scream]
[dramatic music]
Whoa!
What happened to
the Philistines?
It's abandoned.
[Soldier] They left
everything behind.
[bird squawks]
[Soldier] Why would they
leave in such a hurry?
[horse snorts]
What is it?
Amalekites.
[Saul gasps]
[horse whinnies]
Stop!
[Jonathan] Father?
Saul.
No.
Father? What is it?
Father?
We must leave this place.
- Now.
- But father.
I said now!
[intense music]
[Saul grunting]
[Amalekites] Saul.
[Saul grunts]
[Samuel] It's too late, Saul.
No, please no.
[Samuel] The Amalekites escape!
The kingdom has been torn.
[Soldiers] Saul! Saul!
Saul! Saul! Saul!
[soldiers cheering]
Have I not brought victory?
See how we honor God
with this offering!
You honor yourself!
While you feast, the
Amalekites escape!
Just as they attacked and
killed the weakest of us
when we escaped Pharaoh!
You have put your entire
people in danger
because of your pride.
We will never truly be free
with you on the throne.
Don't turn your back on me!
[thunder rumbles]
It's too late, Saul.
Today the kingdom has
been torn from you
and given to another.
[gentle humming]
[Saul gasps]
It's you.
[Saul screams]
[David screams]
It's you Samuel
chose to replace me!
Tell me...
Tell me it isn't so.
I, I can't.
I invited you into my home!
My king.
I loved you like a son!
I have done nothing
but serve you.
You are the anointed king.
Jonathan is just.
Don't!
Say it.
Your words, your, your songs,
they have bewitched me!
Go on.
Are you not man enough to
fight me for the throne?
I have never wanted the throne.
Lies!
You have stolen the
hearts of my people.
Even my own family
loves you more than me.
[Saul screams]
What's left to take
but my crown?
The crown belongs to God.
God!
God has turned his back on me,
and now he has turned
his back on you!
[David screams]
[David grunts]
Seize him, he tried to kill me!
Hey, you!
There he is!
- [Soldier] Get him!
- Come back here!
[Soldier] He tried
to kill the king!
[Soldier] Stop!
Father, what happened?
He, he tried to kill me!
Who?
[Soldier] Come back here!
- [Soldier] Stop him!
- Don't let him escape!
Shoot, son, shoot!
[Soldier] Don't
let him get away!
- David?
It's him, Jonathan.
He's the one Samuel chose
to replace me.
To replace you.
A traitor worming his
way into our hearts.
Finish this, now!
As long as David lives neither
you nor I will be safe.
The crown belongs to us.
[tense music]
[bow fires]
[arrow cuts]
Watch it!
[soldiers screaming] [rumbling]
[David gasps]
The crown belongs to God.
[Saul grunts]
[David pants]
Farewell, my brother.
Seal off the city.
No one in or out
until he's found.
Don't let him out
of your sights!
Come back here!
There's nowhere to run!
[Saul grunts]
[chanting]
Men. Follow me.
[David panting]
Hey, David!
David, where are you going?
Find him!
Put to the sword
anyone who aids him!
Those loyal to David...
Are disloyal to me!
[horn blows]
Find David!
He tried to kill Saul!
It's David!
Run, run, hurry!
[Townsfolk] What's going on?
[Soldier] David
tried to kill Saul!
[Rebecca] David? No! Never!
[Saul grunts]
[David panting]
Hey! Thief!
Stop the thief!
[chanting] [dramatic music]
- Ugh!
- Hey, watch it!
David?
What have you done?
Nothing!
[Saul] Flush out the traitor!
[Soldier] Where is he?
It doesn't sound like nothing!
Eliab, please.
No. This stops tonight.
You've put us all in danger.
If you aren't willing
to do the right thing
to protect our family, I will.
Let go of me.
I need to go.
[both grunt]
[Soldier] Follow me.
Run! Run!
Where is he?
That way.
[horse neighs]
What was that?
Get to Bethlehem and
get our family to safety.
[dramatic music]
[David panting]
[mellow music]
♪ I don't get it ♪
♪ What am I supposed to do
without Your light ♪
♪ Cause I don't understand
how this is justified ♪
♪ I never asked for this,
I wasn't after this ♪
♪ But now I'm hunted
like an animal ♪
♪ But I'm innocent ♪
♪ I'm lost if I go but
I'm dead if I stay ♪
♪ No matter the road,
I won't win either way ♪
♪ Must I go it alone ♪
♪ Will I ever be safe ♪
♪ AHHHHHHH ♪
♪ Why God, why have You
forsaken me now ♪
♪ I'm trying to
feel You somehow ♪
♪ As I run from the
shadow of death ♪
♪ Back to the wilderness ♪
♪ Why God, why would
You lead me on ♪
♪ You show me a glimpse
then You're gone ♪
♪ I'm trying to carry on ♪
♪ Oh why God ♪
[dramatic music]
Ima!
♪ When we cannot
see the other side ♪
♪ Be the star we follow
through the night ♪
♪ 'Til we see the
sun, o Adonai ♪
♪ Hear our cry ♪
♪ When we're lost and afraid
be the way and the light ♪
♪ Show us Your strength
as we walk through the fire ♪
♪ Leader of Israel,
my El Shaddai ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ My God, You have not
forsaken us now ♪
♪ Oh ♪ ♪ You will
work it together ♪
♪ Somehow ♪
♪ As we run from the
shadow of death ♪
♪ Back to the wilderness ♪
♪ My God ♪ ♪ Why God ♪
♪ I know You lead us though ♪
♪ I can't feel You ♪
♪ With You we are never alone ♪
♪ I can't hear You
♪ ♪ You're the One ♪
♪ Who will bring us Shalom ♪
♪ My God ♪ ♪ Why God ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Are You out there ♪
[Nitzevet] ♪ I
know You hear me ♪
♪ My God ♪
[birds screech]
[mouse squeaks]
[bird screeches]
[suspenseful music]
Wake up.
Wake up, dead man.
Wakey, wakey!
Definitely dead.
Good.
Okay.
Now don't suddenly
turn out to be alive
while I'm taking your
sandals, alright?
Dead bodies coming back to life,
oh, scare the heck out of me.
[David coughs]
[Zaydel screams]
What did I just say?
Hey, what have
you found, Zaydel?
A not dead enough dead-man.
[Abishai] You robbing
a defenseless man again?
No, I was looting his corpse.
Big difference.
[David groans]
It's David!
What? What are you doing?
Don't give him stuff!
That's the opposite of
what I'm trying to do.
God favors him today that
we came across his path.
God's favor doesn't
look like what I expected.
[Zaydel grunts]
[David coughs]
Help me.
Wait, he's still got
one of my new sandals!
Ooo!
[gentle music]
[David groans]
[David coughs]
Elhanan, Abishai,
what are you doing here?
Saul didn't take too kindly
to anyone loyal to you.
Or thieves.
He didn't like them.
[chuckles] Nice sandals.
Oh! Thanks!
I had them for ages.
We're glad you're all right.
[all gasp]
Hey you. Huh!
[Abishai] Come on, the
others will want to see you.
Others?
[calm music]
[David gasps]
[outcast coughs]
Who are all these people?
Everyone who's
running from Saul.
[Nitzevet] David! Oh!
Ima!
I missed you so much!
Is the family safe?
[Zeruiah] David!
Ow!
Zeruiah!
You wait until we're kicked out
of the kingdom for a reunion?
You're all here?
[Zeruiah] Well, the
house got a bit crowded
with the soldiers and all.
[all gasp]
Get him some food.
[people laughing]
You come at me with
sword and spear.
- Ah!
- Ow!
That's not how a sling works.
You'll be dead in
a minute, giant.
Now say your next line!
Hmp!
Hey! Watch it.
How's your tapestry working out?
Oh just, you know, way...
Way worse than I thought!
I don't feel like
I'm being woven,
so much as being stabbed!
[Nitzevet chuckles]
Oh I so love you.
Sometimes a thread
is pulled so tight
you think it might snap.
But trust the weaver.
[David chuckles]
I feel like I snapped
a while ago, Ima.
Then trust him to tie
you back together.
[Abishai grunts]
[crowd laughs, applauding]
How can you laugh when we
are being hunted by Saul?
Did you not hear what
he did to the priests?
[light music]
That was my fault.
This is all my fault.
No, David.
I didn't understand at first.
But it's clear our
king has lost his mind.
Look around you.
These people are loyal to you.
It can't be for nothing
that you were anointed.
Abba!
[all gasps]
- What did he say?
- David anointed?
- This is crazy!
- What does that mean?
Is it true?
It's true!
The Prophet Samuel
himself came to my house!
You're the next king?
Yes.
[all gasps]
- David?
- David? King?
- This is wonderful!
- We could go home!
Does that come with
a whole lot of money?
With you as king, we
will at last be free.
Saul won't give up
without a fight.
Civil war then?
What can we do
against Saul's army?
Saul must pay for
what he's done.
David will save us.
God has chosen David.
He is God's anointed!
[echos] He is God's anointed.
He is God's anointed.
God's anointed.
[Saul gasps]
[birds screeches]
[Saul catch breath]
Saul.
[Saul gasps]
What's wrong, sire?
N-nothing.
I just need a moment out
of this wretched sun.
Of course.
[Doeg grunts]
David will save us!
Saul must pay for
what he's done!
We'll gather an army.
We'll overthrow Gibeah.
Finally, we'll be free of Saul.
David is the rightful...
[whistle blows]
[David's followers chattering]
[tense music]
[Doeg] We will scour the
area while you rest, sire.
[Saul sighs]
[tense music continues]
[water fall crashes]
My shadows, these
voices, plaguing me.
[tense music continues]
They will not leave me.
[music intensifies]
[tense music slows]
Anything?
No sign of them, Sire.
My Lord the king.
[tense music]
Why are you hunting me?
Did God not just deliver
you into my hands?
Some urged me to kill you,
but I won't lay a hand on you.
If a Philistine were chasing me
or an Amalekite was hunting
me down, I'd know what to do.
I could, I could defend myself.
But it's you...
My king.
I am not trying to
take the throne.
[somber music]
David I, I.
I
I know, I know, it's okay.
[somber music continues]
What?
[somber music stops]
[dramatic music]
- David, he did it.
- Finally, fresh air.
[Follower] He's leaving,
we can come out.
- I can go home, thank you.
- Thank you, thank you.
[Baker] We must celebrate!
[Eliab] Don't.
[David] Eliab.
Aren't you gonna
follow your king?
I made a mistake following Saul.
Show me it's not a
mistake following you.
[chuckles]
Apology accepted.
Huh.
He won't stop hunting you.
There is one place I
know he won't follow.
[doors creek]
[birds cawing]
[ominous music]
Well, I wouldn't say it's homey.
You sure about this?
Sure that Saul won't
pursue us here at least.
I think I'd rather take
my chances with Saul.
[quiet music]
Hmmm...
It is true, your
most high highness.
The Israelites are unraveling.
Saul no longer has his champion.
Marvelous.
Let's go and pay them
a visit, shall we?
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
[Abishai] David, David!
The Philistines are
marching on Saul!
The largest army I've ever seen!
[dramatic music stops]
[Jonathan sighing]
[sad music]
[children laughing]
[Zeruiah humming]
[gasps] Ah, Philistine!
Ow! Ow!
Take that!
[David] Zeruiah, wait.
David?
Ow! It's good to know
where you land on
the fight or flight thing.
Sorry.
So what do you think?
I think you've lost your mind.
[crash]
Ima, Ima, it's me.
[David and Zeruiah laughing]
Sorry, instinct.
David, what on
Earth are you doing?
You could've given
me a heart attack.
The Philistines are
marching on Saul.
We will infiltrate their army
and turn on them as they attack.
When we deliver this
victory for Saul,
he will know without a
doubt that I am for him.
Everything will be
back the way it was.
The people are divided, David.
Samuel said we'd
be vulnerable if
I'm trying to reunite us.
Is that so wrong?
I will not just
leave Saul to die.
[tense music]
[soldiers grunting]
Quit that.
Okay.
That's a big army.
Their numbers don't matter.
We just have to get to King
Achish and his generals
and the army will collapse.
[crowd shouting] [tense music]
Saul, we heard you
lost your champion.
It's time for a rematch.
A rider approaches.
[tense music] [army shouting]
Where is your father?
Afraid to face us, is he?
He's tired of your talk Achish.
Does it look like
we've come to talk?
I thought we had come to talk.
Well, yes to talk
now, but then battle.
Now I'm with you.
Enough talk.
We haven't come to talk!
We outnumber your
army 10 to one.
Where is the God of Israel now?
Right here, and He
has you doing His will.
What do you mean?
I am not afraid.
If we win, then it
will be by God's hand.
If not, today you are
putting David on the throne.
Either way, you lose.
Get back here, we
are not done talking!
[Jonathan] I thought
you hadn't come to talk.
[Achish growling]
[sighs]
- Come on men.
- What did they say?
They're quaking in their boots.
[clears throat]
I'm.
I'm sorry I brought this on you.
I would rather be
here by your side,
than have you face this alone.
[Saul's Soldier] Black smoke.
Look, black smoke.
The Amalekites must have
found some unfortunate people.
Isn't that coming from Ziklag?
[David gasps]
We have to go back.
Our families.
Oh, this is good, very good.
Did they not wonder why
we abandoned that city?
Anyway, no matter.
Looks like the Amalekites are
taking care of them for us.
[thunder rumbles]
No.
[Achish chuckles]
Well, come on, charge!
[soldiers shouting]
[sad dramatic music]
For God and honor!
[sad dramatic music continues]
We shouldn't have left them.
Our families, we
have to go back.
[sad dramatic music continues]
[vocalizing in Hebrew]
[music intensifies]
[vocalizing continues]
Where are they?
My children.
They've been taken.
[David's followers shouting]
[sad music continues]
Why God, why?
Why?
[sad dramatic music stops]
[tense music]
[Farmer Soldier] This
is David's fault!
[Eliab] Our families.
We believed in you!
It wasn't safe.
You had the chance to
kill Saul at the cave.
- Where is God now?
- We shouldn't have
left them alone!
Why did I trust you?
[somber music] [David panting]
[Nitzevet voice]
Remember when I told you.
God had big plans for you?
They may have been bigger
than even I thought.
[Jonathan voice] Today you are
putting David on the throne.
[dramatic music]
[Samuel voice] Our true battle
is not against flesh and blood,
but in our hearts.
[David grunting]
[dramatic music continues]
[David screaming]
[dramatic music stops]
What do you want from me?
[Young David] I'm
just a shepherd.
[Samuel] A shepherd is
precisely who they need
to lead them back home.
[David breathes deeply]
[tense music]
Where are you going?
To bring our people home.
The Amalekites will kill you.
I'm a shepherd, Eliab.
What can I do but
look after my sheep?
And I trust my shepherd
to look after me.
[Eliab] What if he doesn't?
I'd rather take my
chances following the light,
than choose to live in the dark.
Which do you choose, Eliab?
[heroic music]
[music stops]
Move.
You are cowards!
[tense music]
Scavengers.
Kings fight, sheep scatter.
We collect.
David will come.
He will rescue us.
[Zeruiah gasping]
[David distantly] ♪
The Lord is my light ♪
Told you.
♪ Whom shall I fear ♪
♪ Stronghold of my life ♪
It's David.
- Oh ho, you are in for it now.
- ♪ Though the arrows may fly ♪
- Get on your knees.
- ♪ By night and by day ♪
♪ I will not be afraid ♪
Where are the others?
He's alone?
[Vaizatha] You are
foolish to come alone.
Does it look like I'm alone?
My people are right here
and I've come to show
them the way home.
What did he say?
Why won't he fight?
When I fought Goliath,
it wasn't a boy standing
against a giant.
It was a giant standing
against the maker
of heaven and earth.
So stand.
You aren't alone.
- But I'm scared.
- We can't.
I know you're scared,
but I don't see a
bunch of scared people.
I see mighty men and
women... [grunts].
[Israelites gasping]
No!
I see slaves.
No, let me go.
He's my boy, please.
Take me instead.
This can't be happening.
[David grunting]
[Zeruiah] No.
No.
God, please.
[David grunting] [tense music]
[metal grinding]
Why God?
[David] ♪ The only thing ♪
♪ That I want ♪
♪ Is to dwell with the Lord ♪
♪ If we don't win today ♪
♪ He is still my reward ♪
♪ So whatever may come ♪
♪ Whatever we face ♪
[Vaizatha grunting]
[Israelites gasping]
♪ I will not be afraid ♪
[Rebecca grunts]
[Israelites gasping]
♪ I will not be afraid ♪
[grunts]
[Israelites gasping]
♪ I will not be afraid ♪
[Vazaith grunting]
[Nitzevet gasping]
♪ Follow the light ♪
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
♪ Follow the light ♪
♪ Feel the rushing wind as
you're running into the wild ♪
♪ I will not be afraid ♪
♪ Follow the light ♪
Come on!
Stand your ground!
♪ When the shadows come ♪
♪ We won't run from the fight ♪
♪ I will not be... ♪
♪ Shalom, shalom ♪
♪ Peace be with you
wherever you go ♪
♪ Come on and follow the light ♪
♪ My God, you have
not forsaken us now ♪
♪ Follow the light ♪
[Vazaithat grunting]
♪ So whatever may come ♪
♪ Whatever we face ♪
♪ I will not be afraid ♪
[dramatic music ends]
[peaceful music]
[Ozem] Did you see me?
I was like, [shouting].
So who's going to Hebron?
I'm not doing it.
Raddai can do it.
I always knew David
had it in him.
[Abinadab] I see you
found a sense of humor,
as well as some faith.
Ah, stress weaving again?
David.
[David groaning]
Sorry, sorry.
It's just, you're okay.
[David groans]
[David] Again with the ow.
Ah, deal with it.
The rest of the
family, Abba, Zeruiah?
We're all fine.
[bright music]
[bleating]
Hey, watch it.
Tali?
[bleating]
Way to go girl.
David, come!
There are a few other
people who wanna see you.
[David groaning]
[calm music]
[Zeruiah laughing]
[calm music continues]
[crowd cheering]
[triumphant music]
[Crowd] David, David, David!
[uplifting music]
[uplifting music continues]
[tearing] [music stops]
[David] Perfect.
We're back...
In your hands.
[crowd cheers] [uplifting music]
[triumphant music]
["23" Performed by Phil Wickham]
♪ The Lord is my Shepherd ♪
♪ I have everything I need ♪
♪ I lack nothing at all ♪
♪ He leads me,
beside quiet waters ♪
♪ to a place I can lie down, ♪
♪ and find rest for my soul ♪
♪ He restores and
revives my life ♪
♪ Never leaves my side ♪
♪ Even if I walk
through the valley ♪
♪ Even if I'm lost
in the shadows ♪
♪ I will not fear for I know ♪
♪ You are with me ♪
♪ Surely goodness
and mercy will follow, ♪
♪ follow me wherever I go ♪
♪ I will not fear, ♪
♪ for the Lord is my Shepherd ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ You are my best friend ♪
♪ Like an eagle, you
renew my strength ♪
♪ For all of my days ♪
♪ You are good ♪
♪ and Your heart is for me ♪
♪ And will guide me ♪
♪ In the path of righteousness ♪
♪ For the honor of Your name ♪
♪ Even if I walk
hrough the valley ♪
♪ Even if I'm lost
in the shadows ♪
♪ I will not fear ♪
♪ For I know You are with me ♪
♪ Surely goodness
and mercy will follow ♪
♪ Follow me wherever I go ♪
♪ I will not fear ♪
♪ For the Lord is my Shepherd ♪
♪ You prepare me a table ♪
♪ With blessings
upon blessings ♪
♪ You fill me up in
power of the spirit ♪
♪ And this I know,
You have always been faithful ♪
♪ You will be forever ♪
♪ And I will dwell
in Your house ♪
♪ Here in Your presence ♪
♪ Even if I walk
through the valley ♪
♪ Even if I'm lost
in the shadow ♪
♪ I will not fear ♪
♪ For You are with me ♪
♪ Surely goodness
and mercy will follow ♪
♪ follow me wherever I go ♪
♪ I will not fear
for the Lord is my Shepherd ♪
♪ Yes, the Lord is my Shepherd ♪
[ Psalm 8  by Phil
Wickham playing]
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ We're giving all
our praise to You ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ When I consider the wonders
Your hands have made ♪
♪ The sun, moon, and stars, ♪
♪ all Your glory
on full display ♪
♪ Who am I, that You know me, ♪
♪ and love me, and
call me by name ♪
♪ Lord I can't help
but lift up my hands ♪
♪ and sing out Your praise ♪
♪ Oh Lord, our Lord ♪
♪ How majestic is Your name ♪
♪ In all the earth, You deserve
All the glory and the praise ♪
♪ We sing ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ We're giving all
our praise to You ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ You've established
a stronghold ♪
♪ against all Your enemies ♪
♪ On praises of infants
and children is victory ♪
♪ Who am I, that you know me, ♪
♪ and love me, and
call me by name ♪
♪ Lord I can't help
but lift up my hands ♪
♪ and sing out Your praise ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ We're giving all
our praise to You ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ How great is Your name ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ We're giving all
our praise to You ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ How great is Your name ♪
♪ Is Your name ♪
♪ Oh Lord, our Lord ♪
♪ How majestic is Your name ♪
♪ In all the earth,
You deserve ♪
♪ All the glory and the praise ♪
♪ Oh Lord, our Lord ♪
♪ How majestic is Your name ♪
♪ In all the earth,
You deserve ♪
♪ All the glory and the praise ♪
♪ We sing ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ We're giving all
our praise to You ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ How great is Your name ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ We're giving all
our praise to You ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ How great is Your name ♪
♪ Halle, Halle, Halle,
Halle, hallelujah ♪
♪ How great is Your name ♪